Amie A. Fabah

429 NE Bristol Drive, Lees Summit, MO. 64086

Phone: 816-510-4549, Email: <a href="mailto:csismith1@yahoo.com">csismith1@yahoo.com</a>.

## **SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS:**

I am a board Family Nurse Practitioner in the State of Missouri and Kansas and Board Certified Mental Health Nurse Practitioner. My career in nursing spans more than 15yrs of practical hands-on clinical experience in direct patient care and documentation. I am committed to providing patient centered quality care, especially patients with diverse cultural and socio-economic backgrounds. I take pride in teamwork because of my natural ability to relate well with patients and members of a health care team. I possess lower-level management experience with direct supervision and guidance of subordinates such as Licensed Practical Nurses and Certified Nursing assistant.

## **EDUCATIONAL ACCOMPLISHMENTS:**

**2021-to current:** Doctoral Nursing Student

2019-2021, Maryville University St Louse Missouri: Certification in PMHNP

2013-2014, Walden University, Baltimore Maryland: Masters of Science in Nursing-FNP.

**2006-2009**, Pittsburg State University, Pittsburg KS: Bachelors of Science in Nursing.

1999-2000, Kansas City, KS Community College: Associates of Arts in Nursing.

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:**

Wyandotte County dentition center. FNP 10/2015- present

FNP Licensure 3/2015. 3/2015 to present

Veterans Administration (VA) Medical Center- Medical-Surgical- full time **04/2008- 10/2011**. Lateral transfer to Progressive Care Unit (PCU) **10/2011-Present**.

Lee summit Medical Center- Medical-telemetry- full time status 07/2007 to 4/2008 then intermittent.

St Mary's Hospital – Medical-surgical nursing, full time status from **03/2005-09/2007** then intermittent.

St Luke's Hospital- Orthopedics –full time status from **04/2002 to 03/2007** then intermittent status

Overland Park Regional Hospital- Medical-telemetry, full time status 12/2000 to 04/2002.

## LICENSURE, CERTIFICATION

Board-Certified Primary Mental Health Nurse Practitioner- ANCC Board-Certified Family Nurse Practitioner- American Association of Nurse Practitioners American Heart Association Certified CPR instructor.

\_